thisisbeast.com 2019-12-08

# PRIVACY POLICY

                                            PRIVACY POLICY
Effective March 5, 2015
This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how Beast Technologies S.r.l. (“Beast” or “we” or the
“Data Controller”) collects and uses your information and personal data through a variety of digital
means. By accessing or using Beast’s website, Beast’s mobile applications (including the App “Beast
Strength”) or other Beast’s products or services on any computer, mobile phone, tablet, console or
other device (collectively, the "Device"), you consent to our Privacy Policy.
Beast may modify this Privacy Policy at any time effective upon its posting. Your continued use of our
products and services constitutes your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and any updates thereof.
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and is subject to, the Terms	  and	  Condi-ons.
Any processing of personal data of the User under this Privacy Policy shall be carried out in
accordance with the Italian Data Protection Act 196/2003, as subsequently amended (“Data
Protection Act”).
This Privacy Policy is provided also for the purposes of Article 13 of the Data Protection Act.
1. Data Controller and Owner
The users using the products and services, applications, website, provided by Beast (the “Users”),
including, but not limited to, users of the App “Beast Strength” and Beast’s website, acknowledges that
the data controller of his/her personal data and information is Beast Technologies S.r.l. - Via Cairoli 4,
25122 Brescia (Italy), tax code and VAT number n. 03557770983, services@beast-technologies.com
Beast processes the data of the Users in a proper manner, according to the terms and conditions set
forth in this Privacy Policy, and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized
access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the same.
2. Information collected
We collect the following data and information (collectively, the “Information”):
     a.   information you give us or permit us to access: this kind of information may include, but is
          not limited to, your name, image, birth date, email and physical address, telephone number,
          gender, contact lists, social media information and profile, activity and performance
          information, and when necessary, credit card information;
     b. the data of your sport performances (including, but not limited to, Acceleration, Velocity,
          Power, Strength, Explosiveness, Volume, Lifting, Intensity, Lifting, Density, Average, Power,
          Index of Fatigue 1RM (1 Repetition maximum) ESD (explosive strength deficit) RFD (rate of
          force development) IES (index of explosive strength)RC (reactivity coefficient) ISS (index of
          starting strength) TUT (Time under tension);

     c.   data and information regarding your interaction with, and use of, our products and services.
          Information we may collect in this respect includes, but is not limited to, your telephone
          number, Device identifier and hardware information, IP address, browser type and language,
          cookie information, system type, whether you have enabling software to access certain
          features, access times, referring website URLs, information about your purchases and other
          information about your interactions with us.
The personal data of the Users may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when
using Beast’s applications, software, platforms, devices, and websites.
Users are responsible for any data or information of third parties obtained, published or shared
through Beast’s applications, software, platforms, and websites and confirm that they have the third
party's consent to provide such data and information.
The User is the sole responsible for the correctness, completeness and truthfulness of any data and
information provided, recorded or uploaded or however made available to Beast.
3. Interaction with third-parties for the purpose of acquiring data
We may combine information you give us with other information available directly to Beast as a result
of any upload made by you (on the website, in connection with the purchase, or otherwise). We may
also combine that information with data that is publicly available and data from third parties. We also
collect information about gift recipients provided by the giver.
4. How we collect Information
Beast may automatically collect information within our products and services or stored by your
browser or Device. We use a variety of methods to collect this information, including, but not limited
to, cookies and pixel tags/web beacons ("Collection Tools").
5. Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from children under 13.
6. Using of the Information and data processing
We may use (including using, recording, storing and processing) your Information to do the following:
     a.   allow you to use the features of the App “Beast Strength” and Beast’s websites, such as
          registration of the user in our website, and calculation and recording of your sport and activity
          performances (including but not limited to, Acceleration, Velocity, Power, Strength,
          Explosiveness, Volume, Lifting, Intensity, Lifting, Density, Average, Power, Index of Fatigue
          1RM (1 Repetition maximum) ESD (explosive strength deficit) RFD (rate of force
          development) IES (index of explosive strength)RC (reactivity coefficient) ISS (index of
          starting strength) TUT (Time under tension);
     b. enhance, customize and personalize your experience of the App “Beast Strength”, and Beast’s
          website, and communications with or to Beast;

    c.   operate, provide, improve and maintain Beast’s products and services, including analyzing
         User’s behavior, habits, performances, sport results, sport activity, and trends;
    d. perform any obligations and enforce any rights relating to the sale and use of Beast’s devices,
         products and services, including in connection with enforcement and court proceedings, and
         perform any accounting, fiscal, and legal obligations related thereto (whether merely internal
         or external);
    e.   send you administrative messages and communicate with you about your purchase, account
         information or customer service; send bills (if applicable);
    f.   send you promotional and commercial messages and other information about Beast, Beast’s
         products and services and events (via courier, e-mail, and SMS); send newsletters to you (via
         courier, e-mail, and SMS); perform commercial and selling activities (including direct/indirect
         selling);
    g.   processing/storing/recording of the Information, including for (i) the purposes of developing
         new products and services; and (ii) accounting, legal and tax purposes (invoicing and
         administrative management);
    h. processing/storing/recording of the Information for ‘big data’ purposes and/or for market
         research purposes, statistical purposes and/or to analyze your taste/preferences and habits
         (whether in an aggregated or disaggregated form);
    i.   sell and/or transfer, directly or indirectly, your Information, whether anonymous or not, in
         isolated, disaggregated or aggregated form, to any third-party for ‘big-data’ purposes and/or
         for commercial purposes (including for delivery of commercial materials and direct/indirect
         selling), and/or for marketing/statistical/research purposes, in Italy, or in any country of the
         European Union, Switzerland, USA, Brazil, Mexico, Argentina, Russian Federation, Japan,
         Republic of Korea, Thailand, Indonesia, India.
   It is understood that, to the extent allowed and granted under applicable laws, the data and
   Information on which Beast has been granted the right of use hereunder – shall be considered and
   deemed as owned by Beast, provided the rights and limitations set forth under Article 7 or
   elsewhere in the Data Protection Act or under applicable laws and regulations.
7. Methods of processing
The Information will be processed using tools and procedures which are appropriate for assuring the
security and confidentiality of the data, and may be done on both hard paper copy and using electronic
data processing tools.

8. Place
The Information is processed at the Data Controller’s operating offices and in any other places where
the parties involved with the processing are located.
9. Retention time
The Information is kept for 15 years, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend
or remove his/her data/Information.
10. Obligation to provide the requested data
The Information that we collect from you is required for the regular performance of the features of
the App “Beast Strength” and of the services and features of the Beast’s website. It should be noted that
the non-provision, the impossibility to acquire or the subsequent request for deletion of any data
required, shall cause the impossibility to start or continue any such services, features, and use by the
User.
11. Communication, dissemination and knowledge of the data
The data shall not be transmitted to unspecified persons or entities in any form whatsoever, save as
otherwise provided for hereunder. The data may be communicated to one or more specified persons
or entities under the following terms:
     a.   to Beast’s employees;
     b. to public authorities and agencies (including Garante per la Protezione dei Dati Personali);
     c.   persons or entities who may access the data pursuant to EU and national laws and regulations
          or on the basis of court decisions, within the limits of such laws, regulations and decisions;
     d. in some cases, the data may be accessible to certain types of persons in charge and/or
          involved with the operation of the site (administration, sales, marketing, legal, system
          administration) or external parties (such as third party technical service providers, mail
          carriers, hosting providers, IT companies, communications agencies) within the limits strictly
          required to execute such services;
     e.   to persons and entities who need access to the data for auxiliary purposes to the provisions of
          the regular services by Beast, within the limits strictly required to execute such auxiliary
          services (including but not limited to credit recovery companies, postal services and similar,
          surveillance institutes, ICT providers);
     f.   to other companies which may be appointed, in outsourcing, to manage certain services;
     g.   to the data processors (if appointed), within the limits required to carry out their appointment
          with the organization, following the letter of appointment which assures confidentiality and
          security or their appointment as data processors.
12. Rights of the User

The User has the right to access the personal data which concerns him/her and may exercise the rights
set forth in Article 7 of the Data Protection Act by contacting Beast at the above contact details as
provided by Articles 8 and 9 of the Data Protection Act.
The User has the following rights:
     h. the right to obtain general information on processing operations performed in Italy by
         accessing, free of charge, the online Register of Processing Operations kept by the Italian
         Data Protection Authority (if applicable);
     i.  the right to access his/her own personal data directly from Beast, including for the purpose of
         obtaining confirmation that such data exists and communication of the data as well as to
         know the source of the data and what criteria and purposes apply to its processing. In the
         latter case Beast may charge a fee (“handling fee”) if it is found that no data relating to the
         data subject is held;
     j.  the right to obtain erasure, removal or blocking of any data that is processed in the cases
         provided by the law; if allowed under the law, Beast may retain certain rights on such data as
         strictly necessary for legal, tax, or fiscal purposes;
     k. the right to have inaccurate and/or incomplete data updated, rectified or supplemented;
     l.  the right to have his/her data made anonymous;
     m. the right to object to the processing of one's own data in the cases provided for by the law;
     n. the right to object, in any and all cases, to the processing of one's own data for commercial
         information purposes and/or for sending advertising or direct selling materials and/or for
         market research purposes.
13. Sharing Information
Beast may provide your information to Beast’s subsidiaries and affiliates provided they are located in
the European Union or USA.
14. Service Providers
We may transfer your information to Beast’s service providers to conduct our business. For example,
they may handle credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, market
research, information analysis, and promotions management. We may also share your information to
administer features (e.g. music download, race registration, or workout routine).
15. By law or to protect rights

We may disclose information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required
by law, to enforce our policies, or to protect our or others' rights, property or safety. We may share
information to prevent illegal uses of Beast's products and services or violations of the Terms of Use,
or to defend ourselves against third-party claims. We may also share information with companies
assisting in fraud protection or investigation.
16. Business transfers
Your information may be transferred to a third party as a part of our business assets in a sale of a part
or all of Beast.
17. Protecting Information
We use a variety of security measures, including encryption and authentication tools, to help protect
your information. We use secure servers when you place orders.
18. No Guarantee
However, like other companies, Beast cannot guarantee 100% the security or confidentiality of the
information you provide to us.
19. Public sharing
When you join or use certain services (including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Tumbler
services), you agree to publicly share a basic amount of information, which may include your
username, city location, profile picture, time and location of your internet connection, and certain data
relating to your sport activity and performances. You are the sole responsible party for any such
decision. We invite you to read the privacy policies of those platforms (including Facebook, Twitter,
Instagram, YouTube, Tumbler), because your Beast’s activities and data published on those platforms
will no longer be governed by Beast’s Privacy Policy.
The Beast’s website and Beast’s Apps (including “Beast Strength”) use the social network plugins
provided by Facebook Inc., 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (hereinafter
“FB”). The plugins are identified by a FB logo or the add-on “FB Social Plugin”. When you visit a
page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser establishes a direct connection to
Facebook servers. Facebook directly transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the
latter into the website, enabling Facebook to receive information about you having accessed the
respective page of the Beast website. We have no influence and control over the data gathered by the
plugin. When you click the FB plugin while you are logged in on your FB account, you will be able to
link the content of the Beast webpages to your FB profile or interact with the plugins, for instance by
clicking “Like”, or entering a comment. If you do not want Facebook to attribute your visit to the
Beast website to your FB account, please log out of your FB account.
The Beast’s website and Beast’s Apps (including “Beast Strength”) use the social network plugins
provided by Twitter (hereinafter “TW”). The plugins are identified by a TW logo or the add-on “TW
Social Plugin”. When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your browser
establishes a direct connection to Twitter servers. Twitter directly transfers the plugin content to your
browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling Twitter to receive information about you

having accessed the respective page of the Beast website. We have no influence and control over the
data gathered by the plugin. When you click the TW plugin while you are logged in on your TW
account, you will be able to link the content of the Beast webpages to your TW profile or interact with
the plugins. If you do not want Twitter to attribute your visit to the Beast website to your Twitter
account, please log out of your TW account.
The Beast’s website and Beast’s Apps (including “Beast Strength”) use the social network plugins
provided by Instagram or YouTube or Tumbler. The plugins are identified by the respective Instagram
or YouTube logo or Tumbler or the add-on “Instagram Social Plugin” or “YouTube Social Plugin” or
“Tumbler Social Plugin”). When you visit a page of our website that contains a social plugin, your
browser establishes a direct connection to such servers. Instagram or YouTube or Tumbler directly
transfers the plugin content to your browser which embeds the latter into the website, enabling
Instagram or YouTube or Tumbler to receive information about you having accessed the respective
page of the Beast website. We have no influence and control over the data gathered by the plugin.
When you click the Instagram or YouTube or Tumbler plugin while you are logged in on your
Instagram or YouTube or Tumbler account, you will be able to link the content of the Beast webpages
to your Instagram and YouTube and Tumbler profile or interact with the plugins. If you do not want
Facebook to attribute your visit to the Beast website to your Instagram, YouTube, Tumbler account,
please log out of your Instagram, YouTube, Tumbler account.
20. Use of Cookies
Beast and its service providers may place cookies (defined as a set of data generated by a website and
stored in the hard disk or in the temporary memory on a user's computer when logging in to the pages
of certain websites) onto your computer when you visit the Beast’s website.
The purpose of using cookies is to obtain statistical information and to remember some information
about the user navigation behavior (eg to remember preferences, recognize users, provide a
personalized service based on specific interests, measure traffic and activities during visits to the Beast’s
website, to control and improve our service and to guard against frauds).
These cookies do not keep any kind of sensitive information about users, because they are anonymous.
The information that Beast’s preserves in its servers by means of cookies consist solely of a number
that identifies a user, apart from preferences such as the navigation language used and the date on
which the cookie was sent.
Beast may register your IP (Internet Protocol) such as identity of the computer from which you access
the web, to make the diagnosis of any problem with your server, to administer its web pages and to
analyze user tendencies.
If you do not want to be remembered by the computer as a Beast user it will be sufficient to check the
"close session" every time you leave the website, otherwise, every time you log on to it through the
same computer, the user will be automatically recognized without the need to log in with the email
name and password.
If you wish, you can set your browser to prevent the receipt of cookies and to prevent their
installation on your hard disk. However, if you choose this setting, you may not have access to certain
areas of the website to or can not take advantage of some of our services.

If the setting of the browser has not been adjusted in such a way to reject cookies, the system will
produce cookies from the access to the website.
For more information on the cookies storage, please see the instructions and manuals of your browser
21. Invitation e-mail usage
As a user of the Beast’s website, you have the opportunity to send invitation e-mails that include
recommendations to your friends. The recipient will see the sender address and a personal
recommendation text you might add. Please ensure that you only send these e-mails to real persons
who have provided their explicit agreement to receive these e-mails.
The Beast technology platform will only send e-mails to the e-mail addresses you indicate and will not
make use of this data for any other purpose. You are not allowed to use the invitation e-mail tool to
send spam or information that is in conflict with the general terms and conditions of the business.
22. Changes to this privacy policy
Beast reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users
on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last
modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to the Policy, the User must
cease using Beast’s Applications and software, and can request that Beast removes his/her personal
data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all personal data Beast has
about Users.
23. Communication/Unsubscribe/Opt-Out
Regardless of the settings you select, Beast may send you service-related communications. To
unsubscribe and stop receiving messages, please change your settings or follow the instructions in the
email, text message, notification or other message type. If you have unsubscribed from any Beast
communications, due to production schedules, you may receive communications already in production.
24. Non-Italian Users
Regardless of where you live, without prejudice to any other consent and granting provided by you
hereunder, you also consent to have your personal data transferred, processed and stored in the
country used by Beast for the processing of data, and allow Beast to use and collect your personal
information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
25. Terms of Use
Your use of our products and services, and any disputes arising from them, is subject to this Privacy
Policy as well as our Terms of Use. Please visit our Terms of Use, which explains other terms
governing the use of our products and services.
